<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="tf2reader.png" type="Source"
	xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v4.1"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v4.1 http://knime.org/node/v4.1.xsd">
	<name>TensorFlow 2 Network Reader</name>

	<shortDescription>
		Reads a TensorFlow 2 network from a file or
		directory.
	</shortDescription>

	<fullDescription>
		<intro>
			Reads a TensorFlow 2 model from a file or folder. The
			file/folder
			must be:
			<ul>
				<li>A <b>HDF5</b> (.h5) file containing a (TensorFlow) Keras Model.</li>
				<li>A <b>SavedModel</b> file containing a TensorFlow Keras Model.</li>
				<li>A <b>ZIP</b> file of the directory of a <b>SavedModel</b> containing a TensorFlow Keras Model.</li>
			</ul>
			<p>
				<i>
					The KNIME Deep Learning - TensorFlow 2 Integration is developed by
					KNIME and uses the TensorFlow 2 library. The KNIME Deep Learning -
					TensorFlow 2 Integration is not endorsed by or otherwise affiliated
					with Google. TensorFlow, the TensorFlow logo and any related marks
					are trademarks of Google Inc.
				</i>
			</p>
		</intro>

		<option name="Read from">
				Select a file system which stores the model you want to read. There are
				four default file system options to choose from:
				<br />
				<ul>
	                <li><i>Local File System:</i> Allows you to select a file/folder from your
	                    local system.
	                </li>
	                <li><i>Mountpoint:</i> Allows you to read from a mountpoint.
	                	When selected, a new drop-down menu appears to choose the mountpoint.
	                	Unconnected mountpoints are greyed out but can still be selected (note that browsing is disabled in this case).
	                	Go to the KNIME Explorer and connect to the mountpoint to enable browsing.
	                	A mountpoint is displayed in red if it was previously selected but is no longer available.
	                	You won't be able to save the dialog as long as you don't select a valid i.e. known mountpoint.
	                </li>
	                <li><i>Relative to:</i> Allows you to choose whether to resolve the path
						relative to the current mountpoint, current workflow or the current workflow's data area.
	                When selected, a new drop-down menu appears to choose which of the two options to use.
	                </li>
	                <li><i>Custom/KNIME URL:</i> Allows to specify a URL (e.g. file://, http:// or knime:// protocol). 
	                    When selected, a spinner appears that allows you to specify the desired connection and read timeout in milliseconds.
	                    Browsing is disabled for this option.
	                </li>
				</ul>
				To read from other file systems, click on
	            <b>...</b> in the bottom left corner of the node icon followed by
	            <i>Add File System Connection port</i>. Afterwards, connect the desired file system connector
	            node to the newly added input port. The file system connection will then be shown in the drop-down menu.
	            It is greyed out if the file system is not connected in which case you have to (re)execute the connector node first.
				Note: The default file systems listed above can't be selected if a file system is provided via the input port.
			</option>
		<option name="Mode">
			Select whether the network you want to read is stored as a file (HDF5 or ZIP) or as a folder (SavedModel).
		</option>
		<option name="File/Folder/URL">
			Enter a URL when reading from <i>Custom/KNIME URL</i>, otherwise enter a path to a file. The
				required syntax of a path depends on the chosen file system, such as &quot;C:\path\to\file&quot; (Local
				File System on Windows) or  &quot;/path/to/file&quot; (Local
	            File System on Linux/MacOS and Mountpoint). For file systems connected via input port, the node
	            description of the respective connector node describes the required path format.
				You can also choose a previously selected file from the drop-down list, or select a location
				from the &quot;Browse...&quot; dialog. Note that browsing is disabled in some cases:
				<ul>
					<li><i>Custom/KNIME URL:</i>Browsing is never enabled.</li>
					<li><i>Mountpoint:</i> Browsing is disabled if the selected mountpoint isn't connected.
					Go to the KNIME Explorer and connect to the mountpoint to enable browsing.</li>
					<li><i>File systems provided via input port:</i>
					Browsing is disabled if the connector node hasn't been executed since the workflow has been opened.
					(Re)execute the connector node to enable browsing.</li>
				</ul>
		</option>
	</fullDescription>

	<ports>
		<dynInPort insert-before="0" name="File system connection"
			group-identifier="File System Connection">
			The file system connection.
		</dynInPort>
		<outPort index="0" name="TensorFlow 2 network">The TensorFlow 2 network.</outPort>
	</ports>
</knimeNode>